Just take a look.
你们看吧。
Show tonight
今晚方露
Sitting there alone.
独自坐在那里。
Never had contact with anyone.
从来没有和任何人接触过。
Someone must have touched the glass.
肯定有人碰过玻璃。
But the bartenders and waiters
但调酒师和服务员
has been checked.
已被检查。
There are no suspects.
没有嫌疑人。
I think it's possible for everyone
我认为每个人都有可能
There are too many people in the bar tonight.
今晚酒吧里的人太多了。
My eyes were almost blurry.
我的眼睛几乎模糊了。
wait.
等待。
possible.
可能的。
enlarge.
放大。
Zoom in a little bit and I get it.
放大一点，我明白了。
what have you found?
你发现了什么？
Look what's in the glass.
看看玻璃里有什么。
In glass?
在玻璃里？
Batu.
巴图。
Investigate this woman.
调查这个女人。
In front of and behind this woman.
在这个女人的前面和后面。
Screenshot of Fang Lu’s glasses.
方璐眼镜截图。
OK
好的。
Did you see that?
你看见了吗？
hockey in glass
玻璃中的曲棍球
Sizes vary.
尺寸不同。
During this process,
在这个过程中，
Never touch the beer glass.
切勿触摸啤酒杯。
You see the glass in his hand.
你看到他手里的玻璃杯。
He is there.
他在那。
He replaced the glass.
他换了玻璃。
He also covered the CCTV with his body.
他还用身体遮住了CCTV。
I can't record it.
我无法记录它。
find out
查出
[This woman. ]
[这个女人。]
See if there are any front-facing screenshots.
看看有没有正面的截图。
This seems to be
这好像是
he is very familiar
他很熟悉
In this CCTV environment.
在这个CCTV环境下。
So always avoid it deliberately.
所以总是刻意避免它。
we can't get
我们无法得到
Positive video.
积极的视频。
He is a veteran. what do you think?
他是一名退伍军人。你怎么认为？
This figure
这身材
Something familiar.
有点熟悉。
Is it Chen Ting?
是陈婷吗？
We compared them.
我们对它们进行了比较。
not him.
不是他。
The lights are too dim.
灯光太暗了。
I can't see clearly.
我看不清楚。
Happy birthday.
生日快乐。
Thanks.
谢谢。
welcome.
欢迎。
are you alone?
你一个人吗？
Myself.
我自己。
here.
这里。
I'll give you some water.
我给你倒水。
Thanks.
谢谢。
enough.
够了。
Ayo.
阿哟。
Give us money.
给我们钱。
OK
好的。
Until it was discovered.
直到被发现。
enough.
够了。
great.
伟大的。
Let's go drink somewhere else.
我们去别的地方喝吧。
Ayo.
阿哟。
Visitors from the industrial park opposite
对面工业园来宾
It comes almost every day.
几乎每天都会到来。
Why are these hands so cold?
这双手怎么这么凉？
Lower body temperature.
降低体温。
what's on your mind?
你在想什么？
unconcentrated.
不集中。
I am fine.
我很好。
sorry.
对不起。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Just make up for it
补偿一下就好了
OK
好的。
Scan first.
先扫描。
look.
看。
how much does it cost?
它要多少钱？
I'll tell you after I think about it.
我考虑一下后再告诉你。
What do you want to eat?
你想吃什么？
I just ordered a bowl of noodles.
我刚点了一碗面条。
my stove.
我的炉子。
Yes.
是的。
Sister, Teacher Gao has gone home from get off work.
姐姐，高老师下班回家了。
let me.
让我。
Thanks.
谢谢。
sorry.
对不起。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
I am fine.
我很好。
sorry.
对不起。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Just make up for it
补偿一下就好了
Thanks.
谢谢。
Nowadays, not only are there heart problems;
如今，不仅有心脏问题，
But also very quiet.
但也很安静。
Maybe he's tired.
也许他累了。
My job was not going well.
我的工作并不顺利。
A bit troublesome.
有点麻烦。
Can you work it out with me?
你能和我一起解决吗？
If you can't,
如果你不能，
Leave the problem till tomorrow.
把问题扔到明天再说吧。
Don't think about it just yet.
暂时先别想。
make sense.
说得通。
Our new products.
我们的新产品。
Not sweet dessert, give it a try.
不甜的甜点，试试吧。
Please your mood.
请你的心情。
I...
我...
Don't reject me.
别拒绝我。
OK, I'll try it.
好，我会试试。
Will you remember all the details?
你会记住所有的细节吗？
I remember all customers' preferences.
我记得所有顾客的喜好。
Is this an occupational disease?
这是职业病吗？
Not a job.
不是一份工作。
Available to a limited number of guests only.
仅供少数客人使用。
You are a little different today.
今天的你有点不同。
what is the difference?
有什么不同？
It feels different.
感觉不一样。
Is it because
是不是因为
Drank too much?
喝太多？
Guest birthday.
客人生日。
I had a few more drinks.
我又喝了几杯。
No wonder.
难怪。
Is it so clear?
有这么清楚吗？
reasonable.
合理的。
What else do you want to eat?
你还想吃什么？
Enough, no need.
够了，没必要。
In fact, today,
其实今天，
After leaving the company, I wanted to come here.
离开公司，我想来这里。
See you're not here.
看到你不在这儿。
when?
什么时候？
Around 19 o'clock.
19点左右。
No way, I'm always here.
没办法，我一直都在。
is this real?
这是真的吗？
Have you entered?
你进了没？
No.
不。
I noticed you weren't at the door.
我注意到你不在门口。
It happens that the company
恰巧该公司
He called me and said he wanted to work overtime.
打电话给我说他想加班。
So I didn't go in.
所以我没有进去。
Maybe I'm busy in the kitchen,
也许我在厨房忙着，
Or go to the toilet.
或者去厕所。
perhaps.
或许。
You wouldn't have come in without me.
没有我你就不会进来。
you are here to eat
你是来吃饭的
Or find me?
或者找我？
I just love your cooking.
我就是喜欢你做的菜。
That's fine if you like it.
如果你喜欢就好了。
But this customer,
但这位顾客，
We're almost closing too.
我们也快关门了。
sorry,
对不起，
Your time has been wasted.
已经耽误你的时间了。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
If so, I'll pay.
如果是这样，我就付钱。
Okay, I'll go first.
好的，我先走了。
Until it was discovered.
直到被发现。
this dessert
这道甜点
reasonable.
合理的。
Did he come at 19 o'clock?
他是19点来的吗？
19 o'clock?
19 点？
I was in the kitchen at that time,
当时我在厨房，
Didn't pay attention outside.
外面没注意。
Why?
为什么？
It doesn't taste very good.
味道不太好。
Stone, how about it?
石头，怎么样？
Didn't notice he was gone.
没发现他走了。
Gao Tianyang came to the store today.
高天阳今天来到店里。
He tested me on purpose.
他是故意考验我的。
Are you too close?
你们是不是太亲近了？
What are you afraid of?
你担心什么？
Dia Guk-an.
Dia Guk-an.
He is no ordinary mission target.
他不是普通的任务目标。
You will expose yourself.
你会暴露自己。
You worry about my abilities
你担心我的能力
Or is it my charm?
还是我的魅力？
it depends on how big it is
这取决于它有多大
Some of your energy is on it.
你的一些精力在上面。
Gao Tianyang is a big fish.
高天阳是一条大鱼。
This is no exaggeration.
这并不夸张。
You quite like him
你还蛮喜欢他的
No.
不。
How can you get his attention?
你怎样才能吸引他的注意力？
Yes.
是的。
Don't overdo it.
不要做得太过分。
I know the limits.
我知道限制。
How was yesterday?
昨天怎么样？
What?
什么？
Didn't you go to the bar?
你没去酒吧吗？
is it him?
是他吗？
The body posture is almost the same.
身体姿势几乎是一样的。
but movement
但运动
The difference is quite big.
差别还是比较大的。
Experts can cover
专家可以涵盖
Habits and actions.
习惯和动作。
I've tested it.
我已经测试过了。
No vulnerabilities were found either.
也没有发现任何漏洞。
I'll ask Batu to check it out.
我会请巴图检查一下。
There are CCTV around.
周围有央视。
From 19:00 to 09:00,
从 19:00 到 09:00，
He didn't leave the bar either.
他也没有离开酒吧。
The CCTV in the bar was very blurry.
酒吧里的闭路电视非常模糊。
I found nothing.
我什么也没找到。
useful information.
有用的信息。
so you
那么你
You can only rely on your own feelings.
只能靠自己的感觉。
You must be disappointed.
你一定很失望。
Not that easy.
没那么容易。
found it?
找到了？
Submitted by Chen Ting
陈婷提交
Flight tomorrow morning.
明天早上的航班。
Fly to Paris.
飞往巴黎。
tomorrow.
明天。
Fang Lu is already like this,
方璐已经这样了，
How do you go?
你怎么走？
he submitted
他提交了
Patient exit route.
病人退出路线。
Enter.
进入。
Chief Qin.
秦科长。
Sudden problems.
突发问题。
Chen Ting wanted to leave with Fang Lu.
陈婷想要带着方璐离开。
Go to Paris.
去巴黎吧。
Judging from the current situation,
从目前的情况来看，
Chen Ting left with Fang Lu,
陈婷带着方璐离开，
he wants to continue
他想继续
mengancam Fang Yongping.
mengancam Fang Yongping.
He destroyed the evidence,
他销毁了证据，
Let Fang Lu faint.
让方路晕了过去。
It was all planned.
这一切都是计划好的。
We must act now.
我们必须立即采取行动。
Tahan Chen Ting.
Tahan Chen Ting.
Don't let him get away.
别让他跑了。
Proof that he had been a spy.
证明他曾担任间谍。
almost.
几乎。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
He can't run away.
他跑不了。
most important goal
最重要的目标
adalah Fang Yongping.
adalah Fang Yongping.
So far,
迄今为止，
we should also
我们也应该
dengan Fang Yongping.
dengan Fang Yongping.
He is the leader of this city.
他是这个城市的领导者。
My son did it again.
儿子又这样了。
He must have suffered a lot.
他一定受了很多苦。
me and her
我和她
There is no connection.
没有什么联系。
I definitely know him.
我绝对认识他。
He is not
他不是
Very greedy person.
非常贪婪的人。
I want to talk to him.
我想和他谈谈。
Qin.
秦。
Mayor Fang.
方市长。
You see I came uninvited.
你看我是不请自来的。
It was a bit sudden.
有点突然。
It had become stuck in front of the house.
它已经卡在房子前面了。
There are several possible situations
有几种可能的情况
You don't know yet.
你还不知道。
Can we go in and talk?
我们可以进去谈谈吗？
Come in.
进来。
I still remember you.
我还记得你。
My favorite drink is Pu'er.
最喜欢喝普洱。
Many years of habit,
多年的习惯，
It's hard to change.
很难改变。
Ayo.
阿哟。
Qin.
秦。
in my memory,
在我的记忆中，
After going to Guoan
去了国安之后
It seems this is our first time
看来这是我们第一次
Meet in person.
亲自见面。
So today I came suddenly
所以今天我突然来了
Definitely not for nostalgia.
绝对不是为了怀旧。
if anything happens
如果有什么事情的话
Just say it.
就说吧。
Let’s stop beating around the bush.
我们不要再拐弯抹角了。
How is Fang Lu doing now?
方璐现在怎么样了？
Not in good condition.
条件不好。
I've been thinking lately,
最近我一直在想，
Send abroad.
发送到国外。
Continue treatment.
继续治疗。
we have already started
我们已经开始了
The issue of Fang Lu’s murder,
方禄被杀的问题，
Fang Lu’s case.
方璐的案子。
for a while he was scared
有一段时间他感到害怕
Can't leave Jinhai.
不能离开金海。
investigation?
调查？
Is he involved in the case?
他是否涉及案件？
We suspect he was involved
我们怀疑他参与其中
So-called special forces missions.
所谓的特种部队任务。
Suspect.
怀疑。
Just doubtful.
只是怀疑。
If there is no definite evidence,
如果没有确切的证据，
Thus restricting Fang Lu overseas.
从而将方璐限制在海外。
and continue treatment as normal.
并继续正常治疗。
I don't think this is true.
我不认为这是真的。
how do you know?
你怎么知道？
We have no evidence.
我们没有证据。
if you have evidence
如果你有证据的话
you should not
你不应该
use this method
使用这个方法
talk to me.
跟我说话。
Anda dan Fang Lu, Zheng Guoxian.
Anda dan Fang Lu, Zheng Guoxian.
This is very relevant to you.
这与你密切相关。
I just learned about the situation.
我刚刚才了解情况。
Where is Zheng Guoxian?
郑国贤呢？
I've already explained
我已经解释过了
To the organization.
给组织。
Surrender will not
投降不会
for this case.
对于这个案例。
through further research
通过进一步研究
From Zheng Guoxian,
来自郑国贤，
will realize that there are many things
会意识到有很多事情
unsolvable
无法解决的
With your own strength.
以自己的力量。
So now we suspect
所以现在我们怀疑
behind
在后面
behind.
在后面。
stronger person
更强大的人
from him.
从他身上。
they have already started
他们已经开始了
Discharge procedures.
出院程序。
I already
我已经
Hospital.
医院。
Awasi Chen Ting.
Awasi Chen Ting.
don't let him
别让他
Fang Lu was taken away.
带走了方璐。
understand.
理解。
Aura.
光环。
Halo?
光环？
sorry.
对不起。
our system
我们的系统
Will be upgraded soon.
很快就会升级。
Can you
你可以吗
[after? ]
[之后？]
how long?
多久？
soon.
很快。
Sit there and wait for a while.
坐在那里等一会儿。
I'll call you when I'm done.
我完成后会给你打电话。
Incidentally,
顺便一提，
We work together.
我们一起工作。
Pu Quan.
朴全.
do you remember?
你还记得吗？
of.
的。
He was not then
那时他不是
Go to the Provincial Military District?
去省军区？
I met him last year.
我去年见过他。
In the interrogation room.
审讯室里。
impossible.
不可能的。
Judging from his age, he should...
以他的年龄来看，他应该...
It must be returned.
它必须被归还。
detail,
细节，
I really can't tell you.
我真的不能告诉你。
But I can tell you,
但我可以告诉你，
He did so.
他这样做了。
It's been several years.
已经好几年了。
It's just that I haven't discovered it before.
只是之前没有发现而已。
I remember before we talked about him
我记得在我们说他之前
coward,
懦夫，
There is a reason for this.
这是有原因的。
This kind of psychological burden
这种心理负担
Too heavy.
太沉重。
I am very touched.
我很感动。
He came in and told me,
他进来后告诉我，
After he entered.
他进去之后。
he just felt it
他只是感觉到了
Even relieved.
甚至松了口气。
the most difficult
最难
in reality
实际上是
Exciting days.
令人兴奋的日子。
Because everyone knows
因为大家都知道
If you do a few things,
有几件事如果做到了，
It will definitely leave a mark.
一定会留下痕迹的。
It's like when you're facing a crisis,
你就像面临危机时，
When you face a crisis.
当你面临危机时。
You absolutely understand.
你绝对能理解。
Who are you
你是
What does it imply to me?
暗示我什么？
No.
不。
I'm explaining.
我正在解释。
Mayor Fang.
方市长。
I hope you will turn yourself in.
我希望你能自首。
we doubt
我们很怀疑
Chen Ting dari Yunyi Group
Chen Ting dari Yunyi Group
Ties to espionage organizations.
与间谍组织有联系。
As for you and Fang Lu,
至于你和方璐，
There are relationships
有关系
With Chen Ting.
与陈婷。
Because of Fang Lu’s overseas account
因为方璐的海外账户
dan Chen Ting
dan Chen Ting
With Chen Ting.
与陈婷。
We have
我们有
this information.
此信息。
and reported to superiors.
并已向上级汇报。
At a moment like this, do you ever think,
在这样的时刻你是否会想，
Can Fang Lu
是否可以让方璐
Leave Jinhai?
离开金海？
I know my son.
我了解我的儿子。
he must be
他肯定是
Be exploited.
被利用。
Who manages overseas accounts?
海外账户由谁管理？
Mayor Fang.
方市长。
I understand you.
我理解你。
You are not a greedy person.
你不是一个贪婪的人。
From union to regional director,
您从工会到地区负责人，
From regional leaders to mayors,
从地区负责人到市长，
You have a lot of opportunities for corruption.
你有很多腐败的机会。
if you do it for money
如果你这样做是为了钱
Neither can you
你也不能
Gain appreciation from leaders.
得到领导的赞赏。
so what?
所以呢？
You must be in trouble.
你一定有困难。
Forced suffering?
强行受苦？
If not, you wouldn't do it.
如果没有，你就不会这样做。
You don't even have the courage to call the police
你连报警的勇气都没有
You don’t even dare to call the police.
你连报警都不敢。
Mayor Fang.
方市长。
You are a smart person.
你是一个聪明人。
And the best one can weigh the pros and cons.
并且最能权衡利弊。
If you really want to protect that child
如果你真的想保护那个孩子
The best thing you can do now
你现在最好的办法
Just keep it in the country.
就是把它留在国内。
As soon as he comes out,
他一出来，
This will be
这将是
Someone else’s hostage.
别人的人质。
You are so useless
你真没用
Combating foreign espionage organizations.
打击外国间谍组织。
You feel
你感觉
Can you live well?
你能活得好吗？
worst decision
最糟糕的决定
in my life
在我生命中
Just let my son go abroad.
就是让儿子出国。
I think
我认为
so,
所以，
He will become more independent.
他会变得更加独立。
I can also focus.
我也能集中注意力。
My own business.
我自己的事业。
i never thought
我从来没想到
will hate me.
会恨我。
More unexpected
更意想不到
foreign espionage organization
外国间谍组织
will attack him.
会攻击他。
Come threaten me.
来威胁我。
I want to save the child.
我想救孩子。
There is no other choice.
没有其他选择。
But if I take this step
但如果我迈出这一步
I can never go back.
我永远无法回去。
I know their ways.
我知道他们的方式。
You are a coward.
你是个胆小鬼。
They are a group of animals.
他们是一群动物。
What I'm most worried about now is
我现在最担心的是
It's my son
是我儿子
Ultimately, whether you realize it or not.
最终，无论你是否意识到。
So your best option is now
所以你最好的选择就是现在
is to work with us.
是与我们合作。
you can confirm my child
你可以确认我的孩子
Absolutely safe.
绝对安全。
really.
确实。
He went out.
他出去了。
Hospital West Front.
医院西线。
Chen Ting.
Chen Ting.
We doubt you now
我们现在怀疑你
You are involved in an espionage operation.
你参与了一项间谍行动。
Please cooperate with our research.
请配合我们的研究。
you sure?
你确定？
they absolutely can
他们绝对可以
Fang Lu.
Fang Lu.
I have already contacted
我已经联系过
Experts from Jinhae Third Hospital.
来自金海第三医院的专家。
Ask for directions.
请教方路。
You just need to calm down.
你只要冷静下来。
Fang Lu should be coming soon
方璐应该快来了
will wake up
会醒来
Can I
我可以吗
go ahead
前进
See him again.
再次见到他。
If not, maybe
如果没有，也许
Won't meet again.
不会再见面了。
this...
这...
I really can't make a decision.
我实在无法做出决定。
sorry.
对不起。
this building
这座大厦
very beautiful.
很漂亮。
of.
的。
Ten years ago, things were still peaceful here.
十年前，这里依然风平浪静。
I still remember you.
我还记得你。
When he became district chief,
当他成为地区负责人时，
Build this new city of the future.
建设这座未来的新城市。
Now it has become
现在已经变成了
simbol Jinhai.
simbol Jinhai.
i have done it
我已经做到了
Many good decisions.
许多正确的决定。
But as long as you make a wrong decision,
但只要做了一个错误的决定，
Everything is wrong.
一切都是错误的。
what is it?
它是什么？
Hurry, hurry to the hospital. quickly.
快点，快点去医院。快速地。
OK
好的。
how?
如何？
hold onto.
坚持住。
Yongping, hold on.
永平，坚持住。
No big deal.
没什么大问题。
All physical indicators are also normal.
各项身体指标也都正常。
Pay attention to rest.
注意休息。
OK
好的。
Where is Fang Lu?
方璐呢？
I just saw it.
我刚刚看到了。
He woke up.
他醒了。
The doctor said
医生说
He's fine.
他没事。
It's very close.
已经很近了。
even though
即使
See it from a distance,
从远处看它，
Then we leave.
然后我们离开。
Are you OK?
你好吗？
I am fine.
我很好。
My legs are a little weak.
我的腿有点无力。
Can't stand up anymore
站不起来了
His fever is gone.
他的烧退了。
time flies.
时间过得真快。
instantly,
顷刻，
My son is 30 years old.
我儿子已经30岁了。
Recently,
这几天，
I thought about it seriously.
我认真地思考过。
the two of us
我们两个
Can think of it again
能再次想起
A warm and happy time.
一段温馨而幸福的时光。
At least.
至少。
You know yourself well enough.
你足够了解自己了。
Since childhood,
从小时候起，
your relationship with dad
你和爸爸的关系
Not that close.
没那么近。
So I think,
所以我认为，
i must succeed
我必须成功
success.
成功。
I must
我必须
For my son.
为了我的儿子。
But Dad failed.
但爸爸失败了。
you are right.
你是对的。
If you come back,
如果你回来的时候，
Dad will take you there
爸爸会带你去
Surrender to the organization.
向组织投降。
Explain this to the organization.
向组织解释一下。
The problem will not develop
问题不会发展
Like today.
好像今天。
Who can't come back today.
谁今天不能回来。
Dad was wrong.
爸爸错了。
But I believe you.
但我相信你。
I believe in my son
我相信我儿子
marvelous.
太棒了。
you must follow
你必须遵循
My own opinion,
自己的想法，
walking on the road
走在路上
healthy.
健康的。
You have a responsibility.
你有责任。
responsible.
负责任的。
Dad, don't worry.
爸爸，别担心。
this time,
这次，
I can do it myself.
我能自己做。
leave.
离开。
I still have to take care of it
我还得照顾它
other things.
其他的事情。
Embrace.
拥抱。
OK
好的。
I go first.
我先走了。
Batu.
巴图。
Check.
查看。
OK
好的。
What's this?
这是什么？
This was found at Fang Yongping’s house
这是在方永平家里发现的
di rumah Fang Yongping.
di rumah Fang Yongping.
in the deer head's eyes
在鹿头的眼睛里
In the eyes of a deer.
在鹿的眼中。
I checked
我检查了
from this surveillance camera.
从这个监控摄像头。
Disconnected.
已断开连接。
Access this security camera.
接触该监控摄像头。
night fog
夜雾
Continue past this place.
继续经过这个地方。
mengawasi Fang Yongping.
mengawasi Fang Yongping.
Regarding Fang Lu’s research,
对于方璐的研究，
Also found here.
也在这里找到。
They told me to take advantage of the investment business
他们告诉我要利用投资业务
getting information
获取信息
and get information.
并获取信息。
provide information.
提供资料。
Fang Yongping.
Fang Yongping.
Suruh Zheng Guoxian
Suruh Zheng Guoxian
Introduce me to someone.
向我介绍某人。
Usually they don't really do that
通常他们并不会真的这么做
Contact me directly.
直接联系我。
Basically everything will pass.
基本上一切都会过去。
Zheng Guoxian.
郑国贤.
Guoxian has been paying attention to me for a long time.
国贤关注我很久了。
There's a lot I don't need to say.
有很多话不需要我说。
He will know what to do.
他会知道该怎么做。
I
我
Just use my power
只是用我的力量
Come and help him.
来帮助他。
Not just a recommendation.
不仅仅是推荐。
of.
的。
There are several other cadres here.
这里还有好几个干部。
then,
当时，
Lifted by my power.
被我的力量举起。
WHO？
WHO？
Deputy Director of Tetel Group.
特特尔集团副总监。
Qian Ping.
Qian Ping.
including this type.
包括这个类型。
usually,
通常，
they will meet
他们会见面
They will make it happen.
他们会让这一切发生。
For example, in the name of inspection,
例如，以检查的名义，
We were given an inside tour.
带我们进行了一次内部参观。
Involves some internal data.
涉及到一些内部数据。
wait.
等待。
Chen Ting.
Chen Ting.
And of course on time.
当然也会准时。
Give them some profit.
给他们一些利润。
For example, help them buy
比如帮助他们购买
servers and others.
服务器和其他。
the server
该服务器
Boss Zhang asked me to provide it.
张老板让我提供。
then,
当时，
give them
给他们
for them.
对于他们来说。
Return the money to Ping.
还给Ping钱。
10%。
10%。
Qian Ping.
Qian Ping.
Ayo.
阿哟。
Resort Pulau Xiaoyue.
Resort Pulau Xiaoyue.
Camera on signal tower
信号塔上的摄像头
Does it have anything to do with you?
跟你有什么关系吗？
I'm looking for someone
我在找人
Find someone to install it.
找人来安装。
Anything else?
还有别的事吗？
There is still one.
还有一个。
A model specially built by the High-Speed ​​Railway Group,
高铁集团专门打造的模型，
I did it too.
也是我做的。
This relationship was brokered by Zheng Guoxian.
这段关系是由郑国贤牵线的。
that model
那个型号
dikirim ke Jinhai
dikirim ke Jinhai
Just delivered to Jinhai.
刚刚送到金海。
Express train group.
快车组。
What are they planning?
他们在计划什么？
who knows.
谁知道。
I only know
我只知道
It seems they are very interested
看来他们很感兴趣
High speed rail discounts.
高铁优惠。
How much do you know about Mr. open?
关于先生，你了解多少？张？
We can only communicate through games.
我们只能通过游戏来交流。
Never seen that.
从来没见过。
Is he in Zhenhai?
他在镇海吗？
perhaps.
或许。
He is very considerate
他很善解人意
our actions.
我们的行动。